

Néstor Sánchez Sáenz FullStack Developer | Systems Engineer

Personal details

nesaenz.69@gmail.com

+57 3015168800

Cr 8 # 36-55 Montería -Córdoba

linkedin.com/in/nestorsanchez-saenz-26538a1a9

Skills

Javascript

...

Technologies: Node JS, ●●● Express, React JS, Redux, Next JS, TypeScript, Git, Docker, GrapQL, AWS EC2.

Configuration and monitoring of Cisco, Mikrotik, ZTE platforms.

Cisco, ZTE, Mikrotik equipment configuration.

Languages

Spanish

English

Profile

I'm a Systems Engineer with extensive knowledge and experience in the area of development, using languages such as JavaScript. I have created projects using technologies such as React JS, Next JS, Node JS, Express, Docker, Git, GitHub, and AWS EC2. Currently, I am learning GraphQL, TypeScript, and English. I possess leadership skills, responsibility, and commitment. Additionally, I have extensive experience in the areas of telematics and networks. I am a professional with excellent interpersonal relationships and ethics for decision making, as well as high learning ability and adaptability. I have extensive experience in GPON networks, microwaves, radio links, and configuration and monitoring of Cisco Networking platforms and Mikrotik. My knowledge includes TCP/IP, OSPF, BGP, MPLS, and EIGRP.

Education

Aug 2014 - Feb 2020

Systems engineer

University of Córdoba, Montería

Feb 2017 - Dec 2018

Systems and Networks

San Agustin Technological Institute, Montería

Employment

May 2021 - Present

Systems Engineer

Intalnet, Montería

*In charge of carrying out projects with Backend and frotend technologies such as React, Next Js, Node JS, Express, Docker, GrapQL, Git. *Manage the entire network and server infrastructure of each of the municipalities where

the company is located.

Apr 2023 - Present

Backend Developer

Startups Lab Agencia, Remoto

I use technologies such as Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Git, etc. to build efficient and scalable web applications and APIs. I integrate payment platforms and perform maintenance and optimization of existing code. My focus is on developing secure and high-performance solutions by applying clean code practices and collaborating effectively with the team to achieve project goals.

References

Cristian ALVAREZ HERNANDEZ

MERCADO LIBRE, Bogota, Colombia +57 3206971152, alvarezhernandezcristian1@gmail.com

Juan Diego LUNA CASTAÑEDA

Habi, Bogotá, Colombia +57 318 3397333, juandluna17@gmail.com

Juan Gabriel GIRALDO RIVERA

INTALNET, Tierralta, Córdoba +57 301 6614839, j.gabrielgr88@gmail.com